Finding Aid for the Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Reel to Reel Tapes, 1961-1984
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
- Reel to reel tapes with Mikhashoff as performer or composer, 1961-1984, I.; Item 1-123
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Reel to reel tapes, Tape 013, 1972-01-20, 1 7 inch reel; Container title: 1972 Cambiata Soloists: Shakespeare to Strav. Performers: Cambiata soloists, Isabelle Lipschutz, soprano; Mikhashoff, piano, harpsichord, director; David Bonner, flute; James Chamberlain, clar
    Contents: Haydn: Divertimento a tre; Stravinsky: Three songs after William Shakespeare; Bach: Suite no.5 for unaccompanied cello; Anonymous: The willow song (Othello); Johnson, Hunter: Full fadom five (The tempest); Dowland: Lady, if you so spite me -- Come away, come sweet love -- In darkness let me dwell; Morley: It was a lover and his lass; Mikhashoff: Four figures of a drowned maiden, Ophelia; Weber: Trio, op. 63; Brahms: Songs of Ophelia; Trimble: Four fragments from the Canterbury tales
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_4_013_01am.wav
    Production master files file: ubmu0001_4_013_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_013_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_013_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_013_01-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_013_01-05pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_013_01-06pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_013_01-07pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_013_01-08pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_013_01-09pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_013_01-10pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_013_01-11pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_013_01-12pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_013_01-13pm.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0001_4_013_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_013_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_013_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_013_01-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_013_01-05sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_013_01-06sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_013_01-07sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_013_01-08sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_013_01-09sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_013_01-10sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_013_01-11sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_013_01-12sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_013_01-13sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Reel to reel tapes, Tape 014, 1972-01-28, 1 7 inch reel; Container title: Rice concert Jan. 28 [1972] Performers: Cambiata soloists, Isabelle Lipschutz, soprano; Mikhashoff, piano, harpsichord, director; David Bonner, flute; James Chamberlain, clarinet; Samuel Thiel, French horn; Harry Clark, violoncello; guest artists, Rosemary Silversteen, violin; Wolfgang Justen, flute; Phyllis Herdliska, viola; Paul Schmidt, narrator Recording location: Rice University Printed program inserted; on back of container: Four figures of a drowned maiden (perhaps last piece on concert-half) - check to see if it is the only work on the tape; Concert titled From Shakespeare to Stravinsky Requires checking: 9 works listed, 8 files Derivative files created: 8 (Box 1, Item 14)
    Contents: Haydn: Divertimento a tre; Stravinsky: Three songs after William Shakespeare; Bach: Suite no.5 for unaccompanied cello; Mikhashoff: Four figures of a drowned maiden, Ophelia; Brahms: The songs of Ophelia; Dowland: Lady, if you so spite me in darkness; Morley: It was a lover and his lass; Weber: Trio, op. 63; Trimble: Four fragments from the Canterbury tales
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_4_014_01am.wav, ubmu0001_4_014_02am.wav
    Production master files file: ubmu0001_4_014_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_014_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_014_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_014_01-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_014_02-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_014_02-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_014_02-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_014_02-04pm.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0001_4_014_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_014_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_014_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_014_01-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_014_02-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_014_02-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_014_02-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_014_02-04sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Reel to reel tapes, Tape 015, 1972-06-09, 1 7 inch reel; Container title: 1972 Cambiata Soloists The Broken Consort 1 Performers: Cambiata Soloists, Isabelle Lipschutz, soprano; Amy Winn, flute; Phyllis Herdliska, viola; Mikhashoff, piano, director; Walker Smith, saxophone Recording location: University of Texas at Austin Reel 1 of 2 Printed program inserted; the original description did not include the Copland work on this tape - it needs to be checked - it is also listed as being on Tape 17; 2nd part of program on Tape 16 3 works listed (if Brahms treated as 1), 3 files Derivative files created: 4 (Box 1, Item 15)
    Contents: Mozart: Trio K.498; Koechlin: Epitaph for Jean Harlow; Brahms: Two songs, op.91
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_4_015_01am.wav
    Production master files file: ubmu0001_4_015_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_015_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_015_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_015_01-04pm.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0001_4_015_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_015_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_015_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_015_01-04sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Reel to reel tapes, Tape 016, 1972-06-09, 1 7 inch reel; Container title: 1972 Cambiata Soloists The Broken Consort 2 Performers: Mikhashoff, piano; Amy Winn, flute; Isabelle Lipschutz, soprano; Phyllis Herdliska, viola; Walker Smith, saxophone; Mary Jungerman, clarinet; David Mings, bassoon; David Herbert, oboe Recording location: University of Texas at Austin Reel 2 of 2 Printed program attached; verify contents as 2nd half of concert - see Tape 15 for 1st half of concert 4 works, 4 files Derivative files created: 4 (Box 2, Item 16)
    Contents: Mikhashoff: Tiento para el espejo de narciso; Stravinsky: Three pieces for clarinet solo; Fricker, P. Racine: Aubade for alto saxophone and piano; Poulenc: Trio
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_4_016_01am.wav
    Production master files file: ubmu0001_4_016_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_016_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_016_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_016_01-04pm.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0001_4_016_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_016_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_016_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_016_01-04sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Reel to reel tapes, Tape 017, 1972-06-09, 1 5 inch reel; Container title: Broken Consort 3 1972 Duo for flute + pno (Copland) Performers: Amy Winn, flute; Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: University of Texas at Austin Unclear if this is a duplicate of same work on Tape 15 1 work, 1 file Derivative files created: 1 (Box 2, Item 17)
    Contents: Copland: Duo for flute and piano
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_4_017_01am.wav
    Production master files file: ubmu0001_4_017_01-01pm.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0001_4_017_01-01sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Reel to reel tapes, Tape 018, 1972-02-21, 1 7 inch reel; Container title: 1972 Doctoral Recital (Austin) Part 1 Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: University of Texas at Austin Reel 1 of 2 Printed program attached; 2nd half of concert is on Tape 19 3 works, 3 files Derivative files created: 3 (Box 2, Item 18)
    Contents: Bach-Busoni: Ich ruf' zu dir; Ives: Emerson from Sonata no.2 'Concord, Mass. 1840-1860'; Falla: Fantasia baetica
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_4_018_01am.wav
    Production master files file: ubmu0001_4_018_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_018_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_018_01-03pm.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0001_4_018_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_018_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_018_01-03sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Reel to reel tapes, Tape 019, 1972-02-21, 1 7 inch reel; Container title: 1972 Doctoral Recital (Austin) Part 2 Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: University of Texas at Austin Reel 2 of 2 Photocopy of printed program inserted; 1st half of concert is on Tape 18 Requires checking: 8 works, 10 files; 01-08 is Hungarian Rhapsody no. 19; next two files could be encores Derivative files created: 10 (Box 2, Item 19)
    Contents: Debussy: Images: Cloches -- Et la lune -- Poissons d'or; Chopin: Mazurka op.67 no.4 -- Mazurka op.24 no.3 -- Mazurka op.63 no.3; Liszt: Consolation no.5; Liszt-Mikhashoff: Hungarian rhapsody no.19
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_4_019_01am.wav
    Production master files file: ubmu0001_4_019_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_019_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_019_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_019_01-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_019_01-05pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_019_01-06pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_019_01-07pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_019_01-08pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_019_01-09pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_019_01-10pm.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0001_4_019_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_019_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_019_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_019_01-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_019_01-05sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_019_01-06sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_019_01-07sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_019_01-08sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_019_01-09sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_019_01-10sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Reel to reel tapes, Tape 020, 1972-04-27, 1 7 inch reel; Container title: 1972 Piano Music of 1915: Satie and Debussy Performers: Mikhashoff, piano; Paul Schmidt, speaker; Amy Winn, flute Recording location: University of Houston, School of Music, Arnold Hall Reel 1 of 2 Printed program attached; 2nd half of concert is on Tape 21 2 works, 2 files Derivative files created: 2 (Box 2, Item 20)
    Contents: Satie: Sports and diversions; Debussy: Four etudes
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_4_020_01am.wav
    Production master files file: ubmu0001_4_020_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_020_01-02pm.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0001_4_020_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_020_01-02sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Reel to reel tapes, Tape 021, 1972-04-28, 1 7 inch reel; Container title: 1972 Piano Music of 1915: Ives Concord Performers: Mikhashoff, piano; Paul Schmidt, narrator Recording location: University of Houston, School of Music, Arnold Hall Reel 2 of 2 containing 1 work in 4 movements Printed program inserted; 1st half of concert is on tape 20 Requires checking: 1 work, 1 file, but includes readings before movements Derivative files created: 1 (Box 2, Item 21)
    Contents: Ives: Piano sonata no.2 'Concord, Mass. 1840-1860', edited by John Kirkpatrick and Mikhashoff
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_4_021_01am.wav
    Production master files file: ubmu0001_4_021_01-01pm.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0001_4_021_01-01sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Reel to reel tapes, Tape 022, 1972, 1 7 inch reel; Container title: 1972 The Lost Art of Declamation (Austin) Performers: Mikhashoff, piano; Paul Schmidt, declamation Recording location: Austin Printed program inserted for program titled The lost art of declamation; alternate program title for this concert: An evening of melodeclamation 5 works, 5 files Derivative files created: 5 (Box 2, Item 22)
    Contents: Schumann-Shelley: The fugitives; Schubert-Pratobevera: Abschied von der Erde; Liszt-Tolstoy: The blind minstrel; Strauss-Tennyson: Enoch Arden; Poulenc: Babar the elephant
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_4_022_01am.wav
    Production master files file: ubmu0001_4_022_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_022_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_022_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_022_01-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_022_01-05pm.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0001_4_022_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_022_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_022_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_022_01-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_022_01-05sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Reel to reel tapes, Tape 023, 1973, 1 7 inch reel; Container title: 1973 Amron Chodos / Pipes of Colchis Performers: Amron Chodos, clarinet; Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: Unknown location Contents unclear, no matching printed program Requires checking: identify works. 3 works, 5 files. 01-01 is for clarinet and piano; 01-02 Histoire du soldat. 02-03: Pipes of Colchis Derivative files created: 5 (Box 2, Item 23)
    Contents: Stiller; Martino; Mikhashoff: Pipes of Colchis
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_4_023_01am.wav, ubmu0001_4_023_02am.wav
    Production master files file: ubmu0001_4_023_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_023_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_023_02-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_023_02-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_023_02-03pm.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0001_4_023_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_023_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_023_02-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_023_02-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_023_02-03sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Reel to reel tapes, Tape 024, 1973-06-16, 1 7 inch reel; Container title: 1973 Cambiata Soloists Abendmusic Performers: Cambiata Soloists: Mikhashoff, piano, director; Isabelle Lipschutz, soprano; Diane Tobola, soprano; Amy Winn, flute; David Herbert, oboe Recording location: Trinity University, Ruth Taylor Music Center, San Antonio, Texas Printed program for concert titled Abendmusik inserted; original description did not include the Ravel, Falla, or Ives works Requires checking: 8 works, 11 files. Check how works divided. Includes spoken introductions. 01-01: Moravian duets - 01-02: Vivaldi - 01-03-01-05: Mussorgsky songs - NO SCHUMANN DUETS - 01-06-01-07 two duets from Ravel L'enfant et les sortileges - last 4 files match last 4 works Derivative files created: 11 (Box 2, Item 24)
    Contents: Dvo?ák: Moravian duets; Vivaldi: Motetto: O qui coeli terraeque; Mussorgsky: Three songs: Lullaby -- Evening prayer -- Hopak; Schumann: Duets: Botschaft -- In der Nacht -- Ei Mühle, liebe Mühle; Hindemith: Song for St. Martin's day; Ravel: Five Greek folk songs; Falla: Popular Spanish songs; Ives: Four songs
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_4_024_01am.wav, ubmu0001_4_024_02am.wav
    Production master files file: ubmu0001_4_024_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_024_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_024_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_024_01-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_024_01-05pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_024_01-06pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_024_01-07pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_024_02-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_024_02-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_024_02-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_024_02-04pm.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0001_4_024_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_024_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_024_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_024_01-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_024_01-05sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_024_01-06sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_024_01-07sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_024_02-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_024_02-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_024_02-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_024_02-04sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Reel to reel tapes, Tape 025, 1973-06-15, 1 7 inch reel; Container title: 1973 Cambiata Soloists (Austin) Part 1 Performers: Cambiata Soloists: Isabelle Lipschutz, soprano; Diane Tobola, soprano; Amy Winn, flute; David Herbert, oboe; James Jeter, bassoon; Mikhashoff, piano, director Recording location: University of Texas at Austin Reel 1 of 3 Printed program attached for concert titled Voices and winds: Music from Vivaldi to Hindemith; Part 2 of this concert is on Tape 26; Mikhashoff's Pipes of Colchis from the concert is on Tape 27 3 works, 3 files Derivative files created: 3 (Box 2, Item 25)
    Contents: Vivaldi-Mikhashoff: Motetto. O qui coeli terraeque; Poulenc: Sonate pour flûte et piano; Mikhashoff: Seis caprichos de Federico Garcia Lorca
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_4_025_01am.wav
    Production master files file: ubmu0001_4_025_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_025_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_025_01-03pm.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0001_4_025_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_025_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_025_01-03sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Reel to reel tapes, Tape 026, 1973-06-15, 1 7 inch reel; Container title: 1973 Cambiata Soloists (Austin) Part 2 Performers: Cambiata Soloists: Isabelle Lipschutz, soprano; Diane Tobola, soprano; Amy Winn, flute; Mary Jungerman, clarinet; David Herbert, oboe; James Jeter, bassoon; Mikhashoff, piano, director Recording location: University of Texas at Austin Reel 2 of 3 Printed program inserted; part 1 of this concert is on Tape 25; Mikhashoff's Pipes of Colchis from the concert is on Tape 27 6 works, 6 files Derivative files created: 6 (Box 2, Item 26)
    Contents: White: Duo for oboe and clarinet; Rodrigo: Cuatro madrigales amatorios; Pickard: Maculations on an old Irish dumpe; Hindemith: Song for St. Martin's day; Ravel: Duet of the child and the princess -- Duet of the wedgewood teapot and the china cup
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_4_026_01am.wav
    Production master files file: ubmu0001_4_026_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_026_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_026_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_026_01-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_026_01-05pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_026_01-06pm.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0001_4_026_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_026_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_026_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_026_01-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_026_01-05sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_026_01-06sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Reel to reel tapes, Tape 027, 1973-06-15, 1 5 inch reel; Container title: 1973 Cambiata Soloists (Austin) Part 3: The Pipes of Colchis / Mary Jungerman Performers: Cambiata Soloists, Mary Jungerman, clarinet; Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: University of Texas at Austin Reel 3 of 3 Parts 1-2 of the program are on Tape 25-26 1 work, 1 file Derivative files created: 1 (Box 2, Item 27)
    Contents: Mikhashoff: The pipes of Colchis
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_4_027_01am.wav
    Production master files file: ubmu0001_4_027_01-01pm.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0001_4_027_01-01sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Reel to reel tapes, Tape 028, 1973-03-20, 1 7 inch reel; Container title: 1973 Cambiata Soloists Folk / No.1 Performers: Cambiata Soloists: Mikhashoff, piano, director; Diane Tobola, soprano; Isabelle Lipschutz, soprano; Barbara Bacik, piano; and Svatara Jacobsen, commentary Recording location: University of Texas at Austin Reel 1 of 3 Program titled Folk music: without which not; The contents listed in description are for the entire concert but it is not clear which pieces are on this tape; Parts 2-3 of the program are on Tape 29-30; It's also unclear if the spoken commentary was recorded and where it occurs in the program. Photocopy of printed program inserted. Requires checking: 01: Dvorak - 02: Chopin op. 63 no. 2 - 03: Chopin op. 30 - 04: Ravel - 05-07: Mussorgsky; NOTE: extra 01 file without numeration contains all these contents. Includes spoken introductions. Derivative files created: 7 (Box 2, Item 28)
    Contents: Dvo?ák: Maravske dvojzpevy op.32; Chopin: Mazurka op.63 no.2 -- Mazurka op.30 no.3; Ravel: Chansons populaires; Mussorgsky: Kolybel naja -- Na son grjaduscij -- Hopak; Janá?ek: Listek odvanuty -- Frydecka panna Maria; Smetana: Nevinnost -- Pisen -- Valcek; Dvo?ák: Slovanske tance; Brahms: Zigeunerlieder; Bartók: Improvisation; Falla: Canciones populares espanoles; Ives: Down east -- Charlie Rutledge -- At the river -- Old home
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_4_028_01am.wav
    Production master files file: ubmu0001_4_028_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_028_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_028_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_028_01-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_028_01-05pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_028_01-06pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_028_01-07pm.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0001_4_028_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_028_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_028_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_028_01-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_028_01-05sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_028_01-06sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_028_01-07sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Reel to reel tapes, Tape 029, 1973-03-20, 1 7 inch reel; Container title: 1973 Cambiata Soloists Folk / No.2 Performers: Cambiata Soloists, Mikhashoff, piano, director; Diane Tobola, soprano; Isabelle Lipschutz, soprano; Barbara Bacik, piano; and Svatara Jacobsen, commentary Recording location: University of Texas at Austin Reel 2 of 3 Program titled Folk music: without which not; The contents listed in description are for the entire concert but it is not clear which pieces are on this tape; the 1st half of the program is listed on Part 1, Tape 28 and Tape 30 contains Part 3; It's also unclear if the spoken commentary was recorded and where it occurs in the program. Photocopy of printed program inserted 01-02: Janacek - 03-05: Smetana - 06: Dvorak op. 72 no. 2 - 07: Brahms - 08: Bartok Derivative files created: 8 (Box 3, Item 29)
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_4_029_01am.wav
    Production master files file: ubmu0001_4_029_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_029_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_029_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_029_01-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_029_01-05pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_029_01-06pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_029_01-07pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_029_01-08pm.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0001_4_029_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_029_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_029_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_029_01-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_029_01-05sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_029_01-06sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_029_01-07sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_029_01-08sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Reel to reel tapes, Tape 030, 1973-03-20, 1 7 inch reel; Container title: 1973 Cambiata Soloists Folk / No.3 Performers: Cambiata Soloists, Mikhashoff, piano, director; Diane Tobola, soprano; Isabelle Lipschutz, soprano; Barbara Bacik, piano; and Svatara Jacobsen, commentary Recording location: University of Texas at Austin Reel 3 of 3 Program titled Folk music: without which not; The contents listed in description are for the entire concert but it is not clear which pieces are on this tape; the 1st half of the program is listed on Parts 1-2 are on Tapes 28-29; It's also unclear if the spoken commentary was recorded and where it occurs in the program. Photocopy of printed program inserted 01: Falla - 02-05: Ives - 06: Rossini: Meow duet Derivative files created: 6 (Box 3, Item 30)
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_4_030_01am.wav
    Production master files file: ubmu0001_4_030_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_030_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_030_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_030_01-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_030_01-05pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_030_01-06pm.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0001_4_030_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_030_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_030_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_030_01-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_030_01-05sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_030_01-06sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Reel to reel tapes, Tape 031, 1973-06-29, 1 7 inch reel; Container title: 1973 Composer in Texas / Trinity Univ. Performers: Cambiata Soloists, Mikhashoff, piano, director; Diane Tobola, soprano; Amy Winn, flute; Mary Jungerman, clarinet; and David Herbert, oboe Recording location: Taylor Music Hall, Trinity University, San Antonio, Texas Looks like the tape is flipped with oxide side out? Program titled The composer in Texas: A concert of American music: 1948-1972 Requires checking: 9 files and 6 works? Derivative files created: 9 (Box 3, Item 31)
    Contents: Ray Allen: Sonata for oboe and piano (2 movements) -- Mikhashoff: Beggars' songs -- Hunter Johnson: ?? (3 files?) -- Horvath: Songs -- David White: Five glimpes -- Chinese composer?
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_4_031_01am.wav, ubmu0001_4_031_02am.wav
    Production master files file: ubmu0001_4_031_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_031_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_031_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_031_01-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_031_01-05pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_031_02-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_031_02-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_031_02-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_031_02-04pm.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0001_4_031_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_031_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_031_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_031_01-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_031_01-05sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_031_02-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_031_02-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_031_02-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_031_02-04sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Reel to reel tapes, Tape 032, 1973-04-18, 1 7 inch reel; Container title: 1973 Concert at Rice University (incl. SYNC.) Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: Rice University, Shepherd School of Music, Hamman Hall Printed program inserted; Couperin's Tic-toc and Liszt's Rhapsodie arranged by Mikhashoff 16 files, 16 works Derivative files created: 16 (Box 3, Item 32)
    Contents: Couperin: Le carillon de cythère -- Le rossignol-en-amour -- Le tic-toc-choc, ou les mailletons; Ives: Three-page sonata; Debussy: Images. Cloches -- Et la lune --Poissons d'or; Davidovsky: Synchronisms no.6; Chopin: Nocturne op.55 no.2 -- Mazurka op.24 no.3 -- Mazurka op.63 no.3 -- Nocturne op.27 no.1 -- Prelude op.28 no.24; Liszt: Valse oubliée no.1 -- Consolation no.3 -- Rhapsodie hongroise no.19
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_4_032_01am.wav, ubmu0001_4_032_02am.wav